# **IMAM SULTHONI**

# Frontend Developer | Frontend Engineer

imamsulthoni.amd@gmail.com | +6287727197023 Indramayu, West Java

https://<u>linkedin.com/in/imam-sulthoni</u> https://imam-sulthoni.vercel.app

# Summary

As a frontend developer, I'm happy and used to implementing various UI from figma, responsive, and user-friendly. I have an associate's degree in Informatics Engineering from Politeknik Negeri Indramayu, where I learned the fundamentals of web development and programming. Over two years of experience in creating web apps using React.js, Next.js, Vue.js, Nuxt.js, and other frameworks and libraries, and also integrated data with REST API and GraphQI, and collaborated with teams using agile methodologies. However, continuous learning and exploration is the fuel for continuous improvement.

#### Skills

- · HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript
- · React.js
- Next.js
- Vue.js

- Nuxt.js
- · Redux, Zustand, Vuex
- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap

# **Work Experiences**

#### Frontend Developer (Part time) | Agtran Sdn. Bhd. - Malaysia

September 2023 - November 2023

- Collaboration within the team to streamline project delivery.
- Orchestrated data integration using GraphQI to enhance system efficiency.
- Utilized a tech stack comprising Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Shadon UI, Zustand, and Typescript to drive robust development and user-centric solutions.

#### Frontend Developer (Full time) | Fishlog - Bogor, Indonesia

December 2022 - November 2023

- Developed a web application using React.js, React Bootstrap, SCSS, and implemented Redux Saga for efficient state management.
- Integrated diverse data sets through Rest API to optimize system functionality.
- · Collaborated within a team using agile methodology to ensure synchronized efforts and iterative development.

# Frontend Developer (Full time) | Agtran Sdn. Bhd. - Malaysia

November 2021 - December 2022

- · Developed responsive web-based and mobile applications using some tech stack such as Vue.js, Nuxt.js, and Flutter
- Implemented UI designs from Figma that already created by UI/UX team.
- · Ensuring seamless integration of APIs and GraphQI for enhanced functionality and user experience.

## Programmer (Internship) | PT. Bejana Investidata Globalindo - Bandung, Indonesia

November 2020 - March 2021

- · Contributed to the creation of various client applications by addressing bugs and implementing new features.
- Collaborated within an agile team framework and executed UI/UX designs.
- Utilized technology stacks including October CMS, React.js, Codelgniter, and Flutter.

## **Education**

#### Politeknik Negeri Indramayu | Indramayu, West Java

2018 - 2021

Diploma III Informatics Engineering

Final Project: Implementation of Microservice Architecture in the student tuition payment application at Dar Alquran Arjawinangun Islamic Boarding School.

Certification 2020 - 2023

**Basic Application Programmer** | LSP POLINDRA

## Language

Indonesia - Native Language

English - Intermediate

# **Project History**

## **Agtran Fleetsync Admin**

- · Web application for agtran admin in managing incoming reservations or making revisions, scheduling, master data, etc.
- This web application was created using the Next.js framework (typescript), then the UI framework uses Shadon ui based on Tailwind CSS.
- · Collaborate with Backend Developer in doing data integration.
- · Data integration with GraphQI.

## Fishlog WMS Web

- · Web application for Fishlog warehouse Management System.
- · Built using React.js, and Bootstrap as the UI library, coupled with SCSS.
- · Collaborated with PM, QA, and Backend Dev in building this project.
- · Data integration with Rest API.

## Agtran Web | www.agtran.com

- · A website of Agtran Sdn. Bhd. for car rental services, where users can make reservations for the car they want to rent.
- · Created using Nuxt.js framework, and Tailwind CSS for the UI library.

#### **XCESS Mobile App**

- · Mobile application of Agtran Sdn. Bhd. which is used for staff or admin in managing car reservations by users.
- · This application was created using Flutter, and GetX for state management.

#### **KOPYJAM Admin Web**

- · A web application in the form of an admin dashboard from Kopyjam which is used for management, master data, etc.
- · Created using Nuxt.js, Tailwind CSS, then for data integration with GraphQI.
- · This web application is made from scratch by implementing UI design from figma, to integrating data.